Edwin J. Feulner Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
The Digital Files are comprised of audio files, video files, and text files largely relating to Feulner's speeches and speaking engagements and the 1996 vice presidential campaign of Jack Kemp.
Arrangement of the Papers
This collection is arranged in eight series:
Personal File, 1956-2014
Chronological File, 1965-2013
Heritage Foundation, 1953-2013
Organizations, 1957-2014
Other Professional Files, 1947-2003
Speech and Trip Files, 1958-2014
Writings, 1934-2013
Digital File, 1996-2009
Container List
- Personal File, 1956-2014 (Box 1-30)
  Correspondence, appointment books and schedules, diaries, biographical information, academic files, family papers, awards, press clippings, memorabilia, and mailing lists.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material or topic and therein chronologically.
  - Appointment books and schedules (Box 1)
    - Appointment books
      - 1970-1976, (7 folders)
      - 1977-1983, (6 folders) (Box 2)
      - 1984-1992, (6 folders) (Box 3)
      - 1993-1997, (5 folders) (Box 4)
    - Daily schedules (Box OV 5)
      - 1978-1979, 1981-1983
      - 1984-1987 (Box OV 6)
      - 1988-1991 (Box OV 7)
      - 1992-1995 (Box OV 8)
      - 1996-2000 (Box OV 9)
      - 2001, 2013 (Box OV 10)
    - Miscellany, 1986, 1994, undated (Box 11)
  - Archival agreements, 2010-2014
  - Autographs and inscriptions in books and magazines, mostly photocopies, 1967-1969, 1982, 1992-2004, undated
  - Biographical information, 1964-2003, 2011, (2 folders)
  - Christmas card and mailing lists, 1986-1995, 2002, (6 folders)
  - Diaries, 1969-1985, (7 folders) (Box 12)
  - Dog, 1970-1971
  - Draft status, 1963-1969
  - Education
    - Georgetown University, Washington, D.C.
      - Course work, 1965-1968, (2 folders); (8 folders) (Box 13)
      - Miscellany, 1965-1968, (3 folders) (Box 14)
    - Graduate school applications and correspondence, 1963-1965, (2 folders)
    - Immaculate Conception High School, Elmhurst, Ill., 1956
    - London School of Economics and Political Science, London, England
      - General, 1964-1965
      - Industrial practices inquiry, 1965-1966, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1964-1968, 1975-1977
    - Regis College, Denver, Colo., 1961-1963, (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - University of Edinburgh, Edinburgh, Scotland, 1963, 1976-1981, (4 folders)
    - Wharton School of Finance and Commerce, University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, Pa.
      - Course work, 1964, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1964-1965
  - Family papers
    - Correspondence
      - 1965-1986, (3 folders)
      - 1987-2012, undated, (12 folders) (Box 16)
    - Miscellany, 1965, 1971-2012
    - Farm, 1968-1974, (3 folders) (Box 17)
  - General correspondence
    - 1959-1968, (10 folders)
    - 1969-1972, (8 folders) (Box 18)
    - 1973-1979, (8 folders) (Box 19)
    - 1980-1989, (12 folders) (Box 20)
    - 1990-1992, (7 folders) (Box 21)
    - 1993, (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - 1994-1995, (5 folders)
    - 1996, (1 folder) (Box 23)
    - 1997-1999, (6 folders)
    - 2000-2003, (8 folders) (Box 24)
    - 2004-2008, (9 folders) (Box 25)
    - 2009-2014, undated, (6 folders) (Box 26)
  - Government employment, 1967-1977
  - Honors, awards, and certificates
    - 1967-1987, (2 folders)
    - 1988-2011, (2 folders) (Box 27)
  - Invitations accepted, 1972-1974, (3 folders)
  - Memberships and subscriptions, 1969-2009, (3 folders)
  - Memorabilia from events in Washington, D.C.
    - 1969-1973, 1981-2003, (3 folders)
    - 2004-2009, (2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Miscellany, 1965-2004
  - Personal property, circa 1965-2012, (3 folders)
  - Photography, undated
  - Press clippings and other mentions
    - 1962-1980, (3 folders)
    - 1981-2013, (6 folders) (Box 29)
  - Real estate
    - FMH Properties, 1974-1984
    - Miscellany, 1969, 1974, 1986
  - Residences, 1971-1973, 1993-2012, (4 folders) (Box 30)
- Chronological File, 1965-2013 (Box 30-137)
  Copies of outgoing correspondence beginning prior to Feulner's years at the Heritage Foundation and referred to by his staff as "pinks" because a majority are on pink paper. The years from 1986 to 1988 are absent.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1965-1968, (7 folders) (Box 30)
  - 1969
    - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
    - Mar.-Oct., (7 folders) (Box 31)
    - Nov.-Dec. (Box 32)
  - 1970
    - Jan.-July, (12 folders)
    - Aug.-Dec., (9 folders) (Box 33)
  - 1971
    - Jan.-Sept., (9 folders)
    - Oct.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 34)
  - 1972
    - Jan.-July, (8 folders)
    - Aug.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 35)
  - 1973
    - Jan.-Nov., (12 folders)
    - Dec. (Box 36)
  - 1974, (18 folders)
  - 1975, (12 folders) (Box 37)
  - 1976
    - Jan.-Mar., (4 folders)
    - Apr.-Dec., (15 folders) (Box 38)
  - 1977 (Box 39)
    - Jan.-Aug., (14 folders)
    - Sept.-Dec., (10 folders) (Box 40)
  - 1978
    - Jan.-Feb., (4 folders)
    - Mar.-Aug., (14 folders) (Box 41)
    - Sept.-Dec., (9 folders) (Box 42)
  - 1979
    - Jan.-Mar., (6 folders)
    - Apr.-Sept., (13 folders) (Box 43)
    - Oct.-Dec., (6 folders) (Box 44)
  - 1980
    - Jan.-Apr., (8 folders)
    - May-Aug., (13 folders) (Box 45)
    - Sept.-Dec., (13 folders) (Box 46)
  - 1981 (Box 47)
    - Jan.-Apr., (12 folders)
    - May-Sept., (12 folders) (Box 48)
    - Oct.-Dec., (7 folders) (Box 49)
  - 1982
    - Jan.-Feb., (6 folders)
    - Mar-June, (12 folders) (Box 50)
    - July, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - Aug.-Nov., (11 folders)
    - Dec., (3 folders) (Box 52)
  - 1983
    - Jan.-May, (12 folders)
    - June-Oct., (15 folders) (Box 53)
    - Nov.-Dec., (10 folders) (Box 54)
  - 1984
    - Jan., (5 folders)
    - Feb.-May, (15 folders) (Box 55)
    - June-Sept., (14 folders) (Box 56)
    - Oct.-Dec., (10 folders) (Box 57)
  - 1985
    - Jan., (4 folders)
    - Feb.-May, (12 folders) (Box 58)
    - June-Aug., (14 folders) (Box 59)
    - Sept.-Dec., (15 folders) (Box 60)
  - 1989 (Box 61)
    - Jan.-May, (14 folders)
    - June-Sept., (13 folders) (Box 62)
    - Oct-Dec., (9 folders) (Box 63)
  - 1990
    - Jan., (3 folders)
    - Feb.-May, (14 folders) (Box 64)
    - June-Sept., (14 folders) (Box 65)
    - Oct.-Dec., (13 folders) (Box 66)
  - 1991 (Box 67)
    - Jan.-Apr., (13 folders)
    - May, (2 folders) (Box 68)
    - June-Aug., (14 folders)
    - Sept.-Nov., (13 folders) (Box 69)
    - Dec., (4 folders) (Box 70)
  - 1992
    - Jan.-Feb., (7 folders)
    - Mar., (2 folders) (Box 71)
    - Apr.-June, (11 folders)
    - July-Oct., (9 folders) (Box 72)
    - Nov., (1 folder) (Box 73)
    - Dec., (3 folders)
  - 1993
    - Jan., (3 folders)
    - Feb.-Apr., (8 folders) (Box 74)
    - May-July, (8 folders) (Box 75)
    - Aug.-Sept., (6 folders) (Box 76)
    - Oct., (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 77)
    - Nov.-Dec., (4 folders)
  - 1994
    - Jan., (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 78)
    - Feb.-Mar., (4 folders)
    - Apr., (1 folder) (Box 79)
    - May-July, (5 folders)
    - Aug.-Oct., (7 folders) (Box 80)
    - Nov.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 81)
  - 1995
    - Jan., (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 82)
    - Feb.-Mar., (6 folders)
    - Apr.-May, (6 folders) (Box 83)
    - June, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 84)
    - July-Aug., (5 folders)
    - Sept., (5 folders) (Box 85)
    - Oct., (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 86)
    - Nov.-Dec., (6 folders)
  - 1996 (Box 87)
    - Jan.-Feb., (7 folders)
    - Mar.-Apr., (7 folders) (Box 88)
    - May-June, (6 folders) (Box 89)
    - July, (1 folder) (Box 90)
    - Aug.-Nov., (8 folders)
    - Dec., (2 folders) (Box 91)
  - 1997
    - Jan., (3 folders)
    - Feb., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 92)
    - Mar., (3 folders)
    - Apr., (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 93)
    - May-June, (6 folders)
    - July, (1 folder) (Box 94)
    - Aug.-Sept., (4 folders)
    - Oct., (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 95)
    - Nov.-Dec., (5 folders)
  - 1998
    - Jan., (1 folder) (Box 96)
    - Feb.-Mar., (5 folders)
    - Apr., (1 folder) (Box 97)
    - May-June, (6 folders)
    - July-Sept., (7 folders) (Box 98)
    - Oct.-Nov., (5 folders) (Box 99)
    - Dec., (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 100)
  - 1999
    - Jan.-Feb., (6 folders)
    - Mar., (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 101)
    - Apr.-May, (5 folders)
    - June-Aug., (8 folders) (Box 102)
    - Sept.-Oct., (6 folders) (Box 103)
    - Nov., (1 folder) (Box 104)
    - Dec., (2 folders)
  - 2000
    - Jan., (3 folders)
    - Feb., (1 folder) (Box 105)
    - Mar.-Apr., (6 folders)
    - May, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 106)
    - June-July, (4 folders)
    - Aug., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 107)
    - Sept.-Nov., (6 folders)
    - Dec., (2 folders) (Box 108)
  - 2001
    - Jan.-Feb., (5 folders)
    - Mar., (1 folder) (Box 109)
    - Apr.-July, (6 folders)
    - Aug.-Oct., (6 folders) (Box 110)
    - Nov., (1 folder) (Box 111)
    - Dec.
  - 2002
    - Jan.-Mar., (5 folders)
    - Apr.-June, (5 folders) (Box 112)
    - July, (1 folder) (Box 113)
    - Aug.-Nov., (8 folders)
    - Dec., (2 folders) (Box 114)
  - 2003
    - Jan-Mar., (5 folders)
    - Apr., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 115)
    - May-July, (6 folders)
    - Aug., (1 folder) (Box 116)
    - Sept.-Dec., (6 folders)
  - 2004
    - Jan.
    - Feb.-May, (8 folders) (Box 117)
    - June-Sept., (7 folders) (Box 118)
    - Oct., (1 folder) (Box 119)
    - Nov.-Dec., (4 folders)
  - 2005
    - Jan.-Feb., (4 folders)
    - Mar., (1 folder) (Box 120)
    - Apr.-Aug., (6 folders)
    - Sept.-Dec., (6 folders) (Box 121)
  - 2006
    - Jan., (1 folder) (Box 122)
    - Feb.-May, (8 folders)
    - June-Oct., (8 folders) (Box 123)
    - Nov.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 124)
  - 2007
    - Jan.-Mar., (5 folders)
    - Apr.-July, (7 folders) (Box 125)
    - Aug.-Nov., (6 folders) (Box 126)
    - Dec., (1 folder) (Box 127)
  - 2008
    - Jan. -Apr., (5 folders)
    - May, (1 folder) (Box 128)
    - June-Oct., (8 folders)
    - Nov.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 129)
  - 2009
    - Jan.-Mar., (5 folders)
    - Apr.-Aug., (8 folders) (Box 130)
    - Sept.-Dec., (6 folders) (Box 131)
  - 2010
    - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
    - Mar., (1 folder) (Box 132)
    - Apr.-Sept., (7 folders)
    - Oct.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 133)
  - 2011
    - Jan.-Mar., (4 folders)
    - Apr.-Oct., (8 folders) (Box 134)
    - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 135)
  - 2012
    - Jan.-Apr., (5 folders)
    - May-Oct., (6 folders) (Box 136)
    - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 137)
  - 2013, (10 folders)
- Heritage Foundation, 1953-2013 (Box 138-517)
  Correspondence, administrative memoranda, Board of Trustees files, meeting files, agendas, annual, quarterly, and weekly reports, notebooks, people file, financial records, legal records, office and departmental files, project files, recommendations, résumés, weekly calendars, clippings, subject files, notes, mailings, and printed matter, covering from the early days of the Heritage Foundation until 2013.
  The correspondence is further divided by type: Board of Trustees, general, internal memoranda, members of Congress, miscellaneous, and White House. The general correspondence, known by the staff as "whites," is arranged chronologically by year and therein alphabetically by name of correspondent. Some months are absent from the general correspondence and the years 1978 and 1985-2013 are absent from the members of Congress correspondence. The administrative memoranda, miscellaneous correspondence, and miscellany were created from unfiled material found in the papers. Arrangement is alphabetical by type of material, name of organization, or topic, and therein alphabetically or chronologically.
  - Accounting manual, draft, 1980 (Box 138)
  - Accuracy in Media, newsletters, 1983-1986
  - Administrative memoranda
    - 1977-1989, (12 folders)
    - 1980s
    - 1990-1995, (9 folders) (Box 139)
    - 1996, (5 folders) (Box 140)
    - 1997
      - Jan.-Feb., (3 folders)
      - Mar.-Nov., (5 folders) (Box 141)
    - circa 1997
    - 1998, (2 folders)
    - 1999
      - Jan.
      - Apr.-Nov. (Box 142)
    - 1990s
    - 2000-2005, (8 folders)
    - 2006-2012, (9 folders) (Box 143)
    - 2013, undated, (2 folders) (Box 144)
  - Agenda '83, 1983
  - Aims of Industry, 1979-1988
  - Alamos Alliance, 1993-2000, undated, (4 folders)
  - Albania, 1994-1995
  - Albert Sindlinger & Co.
    - 1979-1980, (1 folder) (Box 145)
    - 1982
  - American Council for Coordinated Action, 1978-1980
  - Analysis, newsletters, 1985-1987, (2 folders)
  - Anniversaries
    - Tenth
      - General, 1983, undated, (3 folders)
      - Photographs, 1983
    - Twenty-fifth, events, 1997-1999
  - Asan Institute, 2007-2012, undated, (5 folders) (Box 146)
  - Asia
    - 1969, 1975-1978, 1986-1998, (8 folders)
    - 1999-2010, undated, (2 folders) (Box 147)
  - Asia and World Institute, 1986-1991
  - Asian Studies Center, 1985-1998
  - Blundell, John, Ladies for Liberty: Twenty Women Who Made a Difference in American History, 2011
  - Board and Administrator, subscription, 1989
  - Board of Trustees
    - Background briefing on Board policy and issues, 2009
    - Board trip planning
      - 1977-1979, undated
      - 1994, Oct.-Nov., (2 folders) (Box 148)
      - 1997, June-July, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 149)
    - Budget proposals
      - 1979-1988, (8 folders)
      - 1989-1995, (7 folders) (Box 150)
      - 1996, (1 folder) (Box 151)
      - 1997-2007, (8 folders)
      - 2008-2012, (5 folders) (Box 152)
    - Committee for Board Commitment and Expansion (Tracy Committee), 2003-2007, (3 folders)
    - Correspondence shared with (Box 153)
      - 1977-1980, (3 folders)
      - 1981, (1 folder) (Box 154)
      - 1982-1996, (5 folders)
      - 1997-2004, (8 folders) (Box 155)
      - 2005-2011, (7 folders) (Box 156)
      - 2012-2013, (2 folders) (Box 157)
    - Expansion, 1978-1994, undated, (2 folders)
    - Financial reports
      - 1975-2004, (4 folders)
      - 2005-2010 (Box 158)
    - Meetings
      - Audit Committee, 2006-2012, (4 folders)
      - Budget Committee
        - 2006-2007
        - 2008-2012, (2 folders) (Box 159)
      - Budget and Audit Committee, 2003-2005, (2 folders)
      - Committee on Corporate Structure and Presidential Succession (Saunders Committee), 2010-2012, (2 folders)
      - Committee on Leadership Succession (Brown Committee), 2004
      - Compensation Committee, 1994-2002, (2 folders) (Box 160)
      - Development Committee, 2003-2011
      - Executive Committee
        - 1978-1985, 1991-1992, (8 folders)
        - 1993-1996, (6 folders) (Box 161)
      - Executive Council of the Committees, 2008
      - Finance Committee
        - 1983-1986, (4 folders)
        - 1987-1995, (12 folders) (Box 162)
        - 1996 -2000, (9 folders) (Box 163)
        - 2001-2002, (5 folders) (Box 164)
      - General, 1992
      - Investment Committee
        - 1990-1995, (2 folders)
        - 1996-2000, (5 folders) (Box 165)
        - 2001, (1 folder) (Box 166)
        - 2002-2007, (8 folders)
        - 2008-2013, (6 folders) (Box 167)
      - Nominating and Governance Committee, 2008-2009
    - Memoranda to trustees
      - 1975-1976, (3 folders)
      - 1977-1980, (7 folders) (Box 168)
      - 1981-1983, (6 folders) (Box 169)
      - 1984-1986, (7 folders) (Box 170)
      - 1987-1988, (8 folders) (Box 171)
      - 1989, (3 folders) (Box 172)
      - 1990, (5 folders); (1 folder) (Box 173)
      - 1991, (4 folders)
      - 1992, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 174)
      - 1993, (5 folders)
      - 1994, (4 folders) (Box 175)
      - 1995, (3 folders) (Box 176)
      - 1996, (4 folders)
      - 1997, (3 folders) (Box 177)
      - 1998, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 178)
      - 1999, (3 folders)
      - 2000, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 179)
      - 2001, (4 folders)
      - 2002, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 180)
      - 2003, (3 folders)
      - 2004, (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 181)
      - 2005, (1 folder) (Box 182)
      - 2006, (3 folders)
      - 2007, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 183)
      - 2008, (2 folders)
      - 2009, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 184)
      - 2010-2013, (5 folders)
    - Notes, 1998
  - Bond, Drew, letters responded to, 2001-2002 (Box 185)
  - Bottom-up Review, 1997
    - "Administration and Finance"
    - "Development" and "Educational Affairs"
    - "External Relations" and "Government Relations"
    - General (Box 186)
    - "Information Marketing"
    - "Public Relations"
  - Buckman, John, Television and the News, 1978-1979
  - Buildings
    - Capitol Towers, 1998-1999
    - Dedication, 1980, May 14 (Box 187)
    - General, 1980-1983, 1992, 1998-2000, 2008-2012, undated
    - Improvements, 2008
  - Calderon, Sila M., 1997
  - Calendars, 1979-1988, 1993-1994
  - Campaign file, 1976, undated
  - Career development at Heritage Foundation, 1996-1998
  - Center for Data Analysis, 1998, undated
  - Center for Strategic and International Studies, evaluation, 1980, 1988-1990, undated
  - Centre for Policy Studies, 1978-1980, 1994-1995
  - Chemical Weapons Convention, 1997
  - Clearinghouse, 1975
  - Clippings (Box 188)
    - Congress
      - 1985-1987, (5 folders)
      - 1988, (2 folders) (Box 189)
      - 1989, undated, (2 folders)
    - Heritage Foundation
      - 1977-1981, (5 folders)
      - 1982-1987, (9 folders) (Box 190)
      - 1988-1997, (10 folders) (Box 191)
      - 1998-2011, undated, (4 folders) (Box 192)
    - Iran Hostage Scandal "October Surprise," 1990-1991
    - Miscellaneous
      - 1975-1980, (4 folders)
      - 1981-2009, (11 folders) (Box 193)
      - 2010-2012, undated, (4 folders) (Box 194)
    - Think tanks, 1980-1991, 2011, undated, (4 folders)
    - United Nations General Counsel, 1991-1992, (2 folders)
  - Committee for the Survival of a Free Congress, 1976-1982, undated, (2 folders)
  - Computer file menu, undated
  - Congressional trips sponsored by Heritage Foundation, 1998
  - Conservative Action Project, 2009-2010, undated (Box 195)
  - Conservative Luncheon Club, 1972-1974
  - Conservative Manifesto, newsletters, 1982-1987, (2 folders)
  - Conservative Opportunity Society, proposals, 1983
  - Conservative Political Conference, Washington, D.C., 1982, Jan. 21
  - Correspondence
    - Board of Trustees
      - 1977-1981, (5 folders)
      - 1982-1995, (12 folders) (Box 196)
      - 1996-2008, (12 folders) (Box 197)
      - 2009-2013, (4 folders) (Box 198)
    - General
      - 1977
        - Jan.-May, (7 folders)
        - June-Nov., (8 folders) (Box 199)
        - Dec., (2 folders) (Box 200)
      - 1978
        - Jan.-Mar., (6 folders)
        - Apr., (1 folder) (Box 201)
        - May-Dec., (8 folders)
      - 1979 (Box 202)
        - Jan.-Apr., (7 folders)
        - May, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 203)
        - June-Dec., (9 folders)
      - 1980
        - Jan.
        - Feb.-May, (7 folders) (Box 204)
        - June, (1 folder) (Box 205)
        - July-Oct., (8 folders)
        - Nov., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 206)
        - Dec., (3 folders)
      - 1981
        - Jan., (3 folders)
        - Feb., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 207)
        - Mar.-Apr., (6 folders)
        - May, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 208)
        - June-July, (5 folders)
        - Aug., (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 209)
        - Sept.-Dec., (8 folders)
      - 1982
        - Jan., (1 folder) (Box 210)
        - Feb.-Apr., (9 folders)
        - May-July (8 folders (Box 211)
        - Aug., (1 folder) (Box 212)
        - Sept.-Nov., (6 folders)
        - Dec., (1 folder) (Box 213)
      - 1983
        - Jan.-Mar., (7 folders)
        - Apr., (1 folder) (Box 214)
        - May-July, (8 folders)
        - Aug.-Oct., (8 folders) (Box 215)
        - Nov., (2 folders) (Box 216)
        - Dec., (2 folders)
      - 1984
        - Jan., (3 folders)
        - Feb., (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 217)
        - Mar.-Apr., (6 folders)
        - May, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 218)
        - June-July, (6 folders)
        - Aug.-Sept., (4 folders) (Box 219)
        - Oct., (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 220)
        - Nov.-Dec., (8 folders)
      - 1985 (Box 221)
        - Jan., (5 folders)
        - Feb., (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 222)
        - Mar.-Apr., (6 folders)
        - May, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 223)
        - June -Aug., (7 folders)
        - Sept., (1 folder) (Box 224)
        - Oct.-Dec., (9 folders)
      - 1986 (Box 225)
        - Apr.-May, (9 folders)
        - June, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 226)
        - July-Sept., (7 folders)
        - Oct.-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 227)
      - 1987 (Box 228)
        - Jan.-Feb., (7 folders)
        - Mar.-Apr., (8 folders) (Box 229)
        - May-June, (7 folders) (Box 230)
        - July, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 231)
      - 1988
        - Jan., (4 folders)
        - Feb., (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 232)
        - Mar.-Apr., (7 folders)
        - May, (5 folders) (Box 233)
        - June, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 234)
        - July, (3 folders)
        - Aug., (3 folders) (Box 235)
        - Sept., (2 folders)
        - Oct., (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 236)
        - Nov.
      - 1989
        - Jan., (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box 237)
        - Feb., (5 folders)
        - Mar., (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 238)
        - Apr., (4 folders)
        - May, (3 folders) (Box 239)
        - June, (5 folders)
        - July, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 240)
        - Aug., (5 folders)
        - Sept.-Oct., (9 folders) (Box 241)
        - Nov.-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 242)
      - 1990
        - Jan., (1 folder); (6 folders) (Box 243)
        - Feb., (3 folders)
        - Mar.-Apr., (8 folders) (Box 244)
        - May, (5 folders) (Box 245)
        - June, (2 folders) (Box 246)
        - July, (3 folders)
        - Aug., (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 247)
        - Sept.-Nov., (7 folders)
        - Dec., (2 folders) (Box 248)
      - 1991
        - Jan.-Mar., (6 folders)
        - Apr.-June, (8 folders) (Box 249)
        - July, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 250)
        - Aug., (5 folders)
        - Sept., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 251)
        - Oct.-Dec., (8 folders)
      - 1992 (Box 252)
        - Jan.-Feb., (8 folders)
        - Mar., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 253)
        - Apr.-May, (7 folders)
        - June, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 254)
        - July, (3 folders)
        - Aug., (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 255)
        - Sept.-Oct., (6 folders)
        - Nov.-Dec., (6 folders) (Box 256)
      - 1993
        - Jan., (1 folder); (6 folders) (Box 257)
        - Feb., (2 folders) (Box 258)
        - Mar., (5 folders)
        - Apr., (2 folders) (Box 259)
        - May, (5 folders)
        - June, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 260)
        - July-Aug., (6 folders)
        - Sept., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 261)
        - Oct., (4 folders)
        - Nov., (2 folders) (Box 262)
        - Dec., (3 folders)
      - 1994
        - Jan., (3 folders)
        - Feb., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 263)
        - Mar., (3 folders)
        - Apr., (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 264)
        - May-June, (7 folders)
        - July, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 265)
        - Aug.-Sept., (7 folders)
        - Oct.-Dec., (9 folders) (Box 266)
      - 1995 (Box 267)
        - Jan., (5 folders)
        - Feb., (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 268)
        - Mar., (5 folders)
        - Apr., (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 269)
        - May, (4 folders)
        - June, (5 folders) (Box 270)
        - July, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 271)
        - Aug., (3 folders)
        - Sept., (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 272)
        - Oct., (5 folders); (1 folder) (Box 273)
        - Nov., (5 folders)
        - Dec., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 274)
      - 1996
        - Jan., (5 folders)
        - Feb.-Mar., (8 folders) (Box 275)
        - Apr., (6 folders) (Box 276)
        - May, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 277)
        - June, (5 folders)
        - July, (2 folders) (Box 278)
        - Aug.-Oct., (7 folders)
        - Nov.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 279)
      - 1997
        - Jan., (4 folders)